<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Suzy Turner]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Suzy Turner]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/suzy-turner/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 20:01:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/suzy-turner/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rocking the gypsy top]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rocking the gypsy top</h1><p>I've always loved the gypsy top but the ones I've tried on over the past few years have left me feeling a little uninspired until I found this one (in the sale earlier this year) from Pull & Bear. It literally cost me a few euros - a total bargain! I put it on for the first time the other evening and decided I didn't like the sleeves so I chopped them off! I think it's much better with a short sleeve. So what do you think? Am I rocking the gypsy top?</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c1554889-cb31-4ed0-a7f7-e99a2d8c106b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c1554889-cb31-4ed0-a7f7-e99a2d8c106b.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1310f386-61a3-4e0e-a79e-d350187f9ca2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 19:58:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A real gem: Cafe Espresso]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A real gem: Cafe Espresso</h1><p>Recently, whilst visiting Sagres, we found a real gem: Café Espresso. Located within the Mareta Beach Hotel, it reminds me of the likes of Starbucks (which, sadly, we don't have in the region - we have to travel to Lisbon for a Starbucks treat!).</p><img src="http://www.suzyturner.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/Espresso-Cafe-4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.suzyturner.com/cafe-espresso/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">590bafb2-a3b1-4be2-83ae-1372a9a7b0f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dressing for the intense summer heat]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Dressing for the intense summer heat</h1><p>Living in the Algarve, I must admit to struggling with dressing for the intense summer heat. On days in July and August, the summer heat can reach (and occasionally exceeds) 40ºC. And that's seriously hot! Although I've lived here 30 years (exactly 30 years last month in fact), I've never quite come to terms with the Algarve summer heat. My body seems to heat up and stays hot like hell all the time. Basically I'm a wreck unless a)I'm indoors with all the shutters firmly closed, b)locked in the bedroom with the air-con on, c)in the car with the air-con on or d)in the shade with a very cold beer ;)</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2ad55abc-f384-4079-967c-7245691ffd14.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2ad55abc-f384-4079-967c-7245691ffd14.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">75751f38-6d26-41ee-ac6c-258934bb5542</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 19:58:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A denim waistcoat and a pop of yellow]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A denim waistcoat and a pop of yellow</h1><p>I love this outfit, mainly blue and a denim waistcoat with a pop of yellow. When I put it together, it made me smile. So when Michael walked in and said I looked 'different' I wasn't quite sure how to take it. Especially as I was hormonal at the time! But whether or not he liked it, I wasn't bothered because I liked it and that's all that really matters, right?</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4c30fd76-9a5e-4bdf-9ef2-191c01a18976.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4c30fd76-9a5e-4bdf-9ef2-191c01a18976.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9de8f0df-428d-4bfb-bd43-83b3a18a2027</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 19:57:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>